Guide to the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Faculty Minutes, 1896-1985.
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Faculty Minutes, 1896-1985
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Faculty Minutes, 1896-1985
24-02-1672
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine
2.0 cubic ft.
Minutes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of meetings of the faculty of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine, 1896-1985.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The New York State College of Veterinary Medicine was founded in 1894.The College was opened for classes in 1896. The faculty has had regular meetings since this date.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of meetings of the faculty of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine, 1896-1985.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Faculty.
Subjects:
College Teachers--United States; Veterinary Colleges--United States; Veterinary Medicine--Study and teaching
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access is limited to faculty of the College of Veterinary Medicine.
RELATED MATERIAL
Another set of faculty minutes is housed in the Flower-Sprecher Veterinary Library. Access to that collection is also restricted to faculty of the College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Chronological.
CONTAINER LIST
- Loose, 1896-1909 (Box 1)
- Loose, 1909-1917 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1896-1909 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1910-1917 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1917-1929 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1929-1940 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1940-1948 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1948-1951 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1951-1954 (Box 1)
- Bound, 1954-1957 (Box 1)
- Notebook, 1932-1947 (Box 1)
- Notebook, 1932-1939 (Box 1)
- Loose, April 1917-June 1925 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1928-June1932 (Box 1)
- Notebook (removed from binder), 1947-1950 (Box 1)
- Notebook (removed from binder), 1950-1954 (Box 1)
- Notebook (removed from binder), 1954-1957 (Box 1)
- Loose, Dec 1957-Dec 1960 (Box 1)
- Loose, Jan 1961- Jul 1962 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1962-Jul 1964 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1964-Jun 1966 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1966-May 1968 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1968-Jun 1969 (Box 1)
- Loose, Oct 1969-Jul 1970 (Box 2)
- Bound, Oct 1970-Jun 1971 (Box 2)
- Bound, Sep 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 2)
- Bound, Sep 1973-Jun 1974 (Box 2)
- Loose, Jan 1974-Sep 1974 (Box 2)
- Loose, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
- Loose, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
- Bound, Oct 1977-Jun 1983 (Box 2)
- Loose, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Bound Index, 1932-1950 (Box 2)
- Bound Index, 1950-1960 (Box 2)
- Bound Index, 1964-1971 (Box 2)
- Bound Index, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
- Faculty Resolutions, 1896-1937 (Box 2)
- Faculty Minutes, 2005-2007 (Box 3)
- Faculty Minutes, 2008-2009 (Box 3)